Raga Mulia Kusuma

Pekanbaru, Riau, 28281 | https://github.com/masraga | real.ragamulia@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/raga-mulia-kusuma-4191b71a0

Fullstack Developer

About

I've experienced 3 year of Fullstack developer, proficient with several modern programming framework such as MERNStack, PHP, and golang. As backend developer i've responsibility for provide a RESTful API and maintenance database relationship. And as frontend, i've responsibility build responsive and interactive web layout.

Skill & Competence

| _ | RESTful | A DI |
|---|-------------|------------------|
| • | RHNIMI | ΔPI |
| • | IXIA) I IUI | / \ I I |

- NodeJS
- PHP
- Git
- Slicing Mockup
- Laravel

- Microservice
- MongoDB
- SQL
- MERNStack
- Redis
- Golang

Work history

Assist.id (Riau, Indonesia)

Back-End developer (September 2021 - now)

- take full responsibility for build CRM application to internal use in assist.id, creating database, providing RESTful API, and deploying system to live production.
- discuss about developing a business requirement diagram for internal system in assist.id
- centralize customer data, such as usage report, payment, etc.
- meningkatkan efisiensi kode program pada sistem assist.id, sehingga sistem tetap berjalan dengan baik dan lancar.
- refactoring old code, for makesure code is clean and follow design pattern architecture
- creating API documentation for other team

Praktek Drg. Nora Indriasari (Riau, Indonesia)

Clinic Administration (Juni 2019 - September 2021)

- record patient information, and medicine data
- creating monthly report for transcation

[Intern] Garuda Cyber Indonesia (Riau, Indonesia)

Fullstack web developer (Juli 2018 - November 2018)

- creating eccomerce application and integrate with payment gateway
- slicing figma design to reactis

Education

Universitas Lancang Kuning pekanbaru (2019 - 2023)

S1 computer engineering (ipk: 3,69)

• absence attendance face recognition with python

SMK Labor Pekanbaru (2016 - 2019)

software engineering

- intern as fullstack developer in garuda cyber indonesia
- participate in ITO competition in politeknik caltex riau